<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts copies on Stars and the Underground</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts-copy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts copies on Stars and the Underground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 11:02:59 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/posts-copy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>News July 2020</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts-copy/news-july-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 11:02:59 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts-copy/news-july-2020/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a night of Post Punk, Goth and Darkwave bands and DJs bringing the dark club vibes party like its 1980, 1990 or 2020.
Stars and the Underground after a successful tour in Australia in 2019 and performances with Drab Majesty(US) and at Shadowplay in Wellington hit the road again to Celebrate the release of their new single &amp;ldquo;Nosferatu Upon Tyne&amp;rdquo;.
They play a unique mix of Post Punk, Shoegaze and Dark Electronic music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update June 2020</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts-copy/update-june-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 13:30:07 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts-copy/update-june-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slowly life is returning to normal in New Zealand, well as normal as it can be. After months in isolation our first meetup as a group occurs tomorrow we will of course exercising social distancing.
We meet at John Mcdermott studio&amp;rsquo;s to mix the first song off our new album. We are excited&amp;hellip;
We have a collection of material accumulating both recorded and in demo form which we will work through to complete and decide whether we will use it for the album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News: New Single</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts-copy/_news-new-single-31-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 15:27:44 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts-copy/_news-new-single-31-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>We recorded a new single &amp;ldquo;Nosferatu Upon Tyne&amp;rdquo; at Arch Hill Recording Studios in Auckland with John McDermott.
The recording session was the first for our new bass player Ari and our keyboard player Cat.
We enjoyed track laying with John and the drums he laid down were awesome.
Another session will be required to tie some loose ends on the track and to mix.
Then the virus hit&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>